## **ITUMELENG MATHEBA**

Address: 78 Gardenia Avenue, Flora Park, Polokwane, 0699

**Phone:** 071 876 0048

**Email:** tumimatheba@gmail.com

#### **PROFILE**

I'm an enthusiastic aspiring software developer with a background in technical support as an IT technician with just under 5 years career experience in LAN and Desktop support as well as IT Help Desk support. I have excellent organizational and problem solving skills. I work well in team Environments and exhibit a strong work ethic.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

05/2014 - 03/2018

### LAN and Desktop Technical Support, **Department Of Health.**

Responsibilities:

- Actively assist clients with any computer related issues.
- Responsible for compiling monthly reports for calls logged and resolved.
- Responsible for establishing needs and procuring IT equipment for users in the hospital.

05/2018 - 12/2018

#### **Customer Care, Amazon World Wide Operations.** Responsibilities:

- Actively assist customers navigate the Amazon website for online shopping.
- Assist customers resolve any order issues.

07/2019 - 03/2021

#### **ESL Teacher, Cambly.**

Responsibilities:

Teach English as a foreign language to Asian students.

**EDUCATION** 

11/2020

Umuzi Bootcamp Upskilling Program, Umuzi.

02/2013

**Certified as PC Technician**, Advanced Technology Training Institute(ATTI).

12/2012

Matric, Northern Academy High School.

07/2019

**TEFL certificate**, i-to-i.

# ADDITIONAL SKILLS

Novice knowledge of JavaScript, Python, HTML and CSS.

#### REFERENCES

References available on request